Hello friends, you are heartily welcome to the India YouTube channel.
You are watching the
Stock India YouTube channel. If you are
visiting the channel for the first time, then hit the bell icon and
select all.
[Music] Let's
start today's video.
You have seen gravity in it.
Today the market was expecting the result of the RBI's MPC meeting.
Today, the
results of the meeting of the MPC and the RBI are being seen in the meeting. The
rate height that was taken in the RBI meeting is as per the
market. Arvind
calculated the rate at line 25.35. Arvind calculated the
rate accordingly. But then
why did the market fall in it? Then the gravity in the index. The
reason for this is that Arvind's
policy for the future, that the rate
height will
remain the same from now onwards, that is, in the future, the
RBI's
Shashikant Das and his chairperson
said that the inflation that is there right now is still there
and will continue to be there in the future as well.  The trend of rates going high will continue in the future as
well. So, due to this
commitment from RBI,
due to which it was seen to be dry and in that, despite the
rates being high and low,
you did
not see any movement in the market. But the
market opened today around the previous close
and after the RBI statement came, there was a slight decline
in the market.
Overall, due to
this, the sentiment related to the police station was
not positive, due to which the
market saw a decline today. The
Arabians say that the
inflation figure is still
not down, due to this, the rates will
remain the same in the future as well. So, let us see what the RBI has said on the market today.
Today, Mr. Shashikant Das and
he have also said that if we
look at the policy of the monitor, the Arab
rate is higher by 35 and the previous rate was
hovering around 590 and it has
increased from 590.  After becoming 35 and the report which has become
around 25, 6.25, so if we
look at it, then the
impact of the rate will be
seen in the future as well because now the
banks which
give loans to the relative sectors, the loans required by the banks are going to become
very expensive and this is the
reason, so the
reason for this will be that due to
increase in the loan amount, the loan amount is now very expensive due to
increase in that amount and there has been a
significant decline in these two stocks,
these 35, so they told their rate that the
rate of 35 has been increased to 6
and the reason for this is that the
inflation figure is low right now, there is
still inflation, so the rate will keep increasing in the future as well, the
target of retail inflation is
more than Hanuman right now, but the
future finance is bound to happen
and in the estimate of 2023, the
Indian
market also
got to see negative news, that is, the yesterday  If you look at the
ratings they have given on Indian GDP,
but Arvind, in your statement today, the
growth estimate of Indian GDP has been given at 7%,
so this is also a negative news for the market,
and
because of this,
despite the rate hike in the market today as per the market,
you have not seen any rise in the index. So
now that the repo rate has gone up, which is a big increase in the repo rate,
which sector will be affected by it? If
we discuss this now, then
it is being told directly that the
sectors which will be directly affected are, firstly, the
loans of the banks will become very expensive,
so people will reduce their loan taking
and the
effect of this will already be seen in two sectors,
one in the realty and properties
sector and secondly, the
people who take loans for alternatives, so its effect can be seen on the sector as well, so
it has fallen the most on these two stocks
and we will also look at this, if we
talk about Tata Motors.  The impact of voter
part photos was
seen and in Tata Motors
also, it has been seen almost more than 1 1/2%,
similar is seen on relative basis, if we
look at the reality also, then
now to see the ground of three to four percent in this
and the rate which is being seen the
most impact will be seen on the
property sector related
sector and so if we
look at this today, the market is seeing a
growth of about four percent and if we
talk about Godrej Properties, then Godrej
Properties is also seeing a growth of about 25%,
so the highest
impact of the rate, bike stream, the
chapter related to the properties of these sectors is the auto
sector, those components are because
if the demand in the auto sector will be less and if the demand is
less
then overall the
trains can be seen to be more affected
and now we talk about Paytm and
today there is big news on Ttml, that is coming out, there is
a news update on the table also,
that is being seen  TTM has
offered it for business,
providing services which are 5G internet based
cloud ID based digital services.
Microsoft has made a business offer
in which it has said that for small and
medium enterprises, small and medium
businesses, they should avail digital
services from digital services.
This is the above agreement
of TTM
with Microsoft. So, these
cloud based computing services,
storage, networking related to thousands,
one to one and a half percent, you have seen it. So,
in this agreement between TTM and Microsoft, it is given which
services are offered. We have a
look at the services. Microsoft Azure offers as well as
computing services
related to storage, networking resources
on demand and 5G networking services which are in the
future, so many services related to 5G are going to
increase a lot in the times to come, so understand this, there will be
services and
services like and Prem you, the
migration of Microsoft, which is the
service public cloud, which  Migration
Storage Service Aman Adarsh ​​which is 5G based
services, this has been seen, if we
talk about Ttml, then today there is a
rise in the stock of T-Table
and due to this news, if we look at today then this
news is also covered, Tata Tele
Business Services to offer Microsoft
Azure to small and medium enterprises
and all the industries of small and medium enterprises, the
talks about providing 5G related services, the offer of which has been made,
due to this news you have
seen a rise of 2% from the date in T-Table today and
we now talk about Kal Technology,
Kal Technology is
definitely getting it, it has
also joined hands with Intel and Mahavir, an
enterprise which is 5G, 5G
solution, 5G network related
services related hand,
so see Kal
Tech,
Kal Tech announced Kal Techno
partnership with Intel Corporation and
Tata Corporation, the partnership between them is
network solution
service provider, so this is 5G  It will be related to the network, they are
going to arrange a fund of 5000 crores
and there is also a news on Axis
regarding the credit rating, the credit rating,
and the rating that Axis Bank has received, it has received a
positive rating
and Axis Bank has received rating
action from Indian Indian Ratings, that is,
a teacher is being
seen from the rating agency Indian India Ratings and let's talk about these
efforts, what is being
seen tomorrow, it will happen from tomorrow,
Infosys share buy-back open today, that is
from today, whatever was in the session of Bhai, that is
on and this WiFi has
started, that's all
in the video and all the news that was there has been
covered now, if you liked the video then do
like and share it
and if you visit the channel for the first time then
subscribe and also set the bell icon
and with the latest updates and we will
meet again in the next video, till then,
hello